[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
There's another reason why you want Mikoy gone so badly.
Like what?
And you think,
you can make me do what you want because I'm under your spell.
As far as I know, she's connected to Chiara Valtrovi.
And if her information is correct, then we can take her down.
They want something in return.
I'm here to ask for your help.
Tell me everything you know!
But I can take you to someone who knows where they are.
-Who? -Vicky Corales.
She's known as,
Widow's Maid.
The tracker I planted on you, has been activated, Chiara.
Looks like my sweetheart still hasn't changed.
If I didn't know you, I'd think you're still that waiter…
Follow me.
Well, I guess,
you have changed.
A little.
Looks like I'm at a disadvantage in this fight.
Dad Mario would be so proud.
How dare you even say his name?
We treated you like family.
I loved you,
unconditionally.
And then you killed my father.
If only I had known, and if I could turn back time,
So I'm just supposed to forgive you?
Just forget everything?
That wasn't what I meant.
I'm not stupid!
Okay?
Tell me,
why I shouldn't blow your brains out right now.
Where are Mikoy and Chiara?
Are you going to talk, or do you want to get hurt?
Let's all calm down.
I know you want to find Mikoy and Chiara.
But this isn't the way to extract information from her.
But I'm running out of time,
I need to extract the information I need.
At this point,
Mom, please.
Don't say anything if you don't have anything good to say.
I already spoke with Agent Dara.
This isn't just about Dad Mario.
You're angry
because you think I abandoned you.
Why? Isn't it true?
You only used me for your ambition.
You manipulated me.
You don't love me.
for what you really wanted,
to rule over criminals!
You think so little of me, sweetheart.
I'm done with all your games.
I'm done with you making a fool of me.
I did that
so you wouldn't get dragged into my messed-up life!
Because if I kept fighting for our love,
you'd only get hurt even more!
And I'd never forgive myself
if anything happened to you!
Enough, Chiara.
I'm tired of all your lies.
Now,
you'll pay for everything you've done.
Looks like nothing can change your mind, sweetheart.
I'll use this
to make you feel
what you did to my father.
That's why I targeted it.
Now you'll have a hard time moving,
and the advantage is mine.
Looks like we're evenly matched now.
Why?
Why did you turn your back on me?
But I only ended up hurting you more.
I never should've met you.
I never should've
dragged you into my world.
I promise,
I will never stop
loving you.
Chiara!
Chiara, are you okay?
Leave me here as a decoy!
After everything you've done?
Now you want to play the hero?
We have to fight.
We don't have a choice
because I'm not leaving you.
We'll both end up dead!
But we still have a chance.
After all, La Fornarina is on my side again.
Okay. Well, that makes me feel confident.
Because apparently,
I'm backed by the Philippines' national drunkard.
You idiot, Mikoy.
Don't you dare die.
Wait for me.
Looks like we screwed up, my love.
We wasted so much time.
Because even if it wasn't forever…
Find me.
Senator Quintin.
I'm sorry, but there's a warrant for your arrest.
Is this a joke?
Wait, wait, wait!
What is this? This isn't real!
I'm innocent!
I'm not a member of any syndicate!
This is bullshit!
Give me that.
Put the handcuffs on him.
Handcuffs? Is this a prank?
Agent Djanggo.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say may be used against you.
With the death of Chiara Valtrovi,
we thought it was a dead end for the agency.
Well, apparently,
she had set up
what we call in law enforcement
a dead man's switch.
In the event of her death…
…that conducted the pursuit and arrest
of Concordat officials and leaders.
We have arrested hundreds of significant figures
from various syndicates.
Not only in Europe,
but also in Asia and the Middle East.
And Chiara didn't just provide information about the key figures.
Good for you. And…
You're free.
Mom, please.
I just wanted to know if you were okay.
I would've been better if my own daughter hadn't screwed me over.
Mom, what's done is done.
Be angry if you want.
But as for me,
I'll always be here,
and I'll always be your son.
You better.
You're the one who put me here.
So make sure
you visit me every day.
I'll never leave you, Mom.
By the way, what happened to Chiara and Mikoy?
Mikoy and Chiara are dead!
Because of your illegal operations!
And your deal with Vickey Corales.
That's not true!
I know you know
that Mikoy and Chiara are still alive.
Chiara! Mikoy!
Medic! Call a medic! Hurry!
I know Mikoy and Chiara are still alive!
Whether Mikoy and Chiara are dead or alive…
Because I'll make sure you rot in prison!
Mikoy and Chiara are still alive!
They're still alive!
Carlota!
So, General, what you're trying to tell me
is that Chiara went back to the Concordat,
not to betray us or Mikoy, but
to discover the ins and outs of their operation?
Maybe so she could take them down too? Right?
Cliche as it may seem,
she was able to bring down
some of the biggest syndicates…
Are Chiara and Mikoy truly dead?
I hope wherever you are, Dad,
you are proud of me.
Because my mission is to continue yours.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you for always watching over me.
Give Mom a kiss for me.
I'm sure she'll be pissed.
We should demand to repatriate Chiara’s body.
You might be forgetting…
What?
Maybe,
Chiara and Mikoy are still alive.
What are you talking about? You know you're just hungry.
Where's our order? Hold on.
Waiter.
Why?
Why did you suddenly space out? What happened?
Let's go!
-Let's go in here. Here. -Hey, wait!
Let me play too, Chiara!
What are you talking about?
Someone might hear you!
Pepito, come on!
Oh, right!
Clara!
See what you did?
Only this small?
Grandma's here!
Let's go!
-Let's eat. Come on. -Thanks, Mom.
-Let's eat. -It's time to eat. Let's go.
Rice cakes!
Is that good?
Yes, it's delicious!
You'll forget your own name!
Then let's buy some!
-What's that? -I'll take one!
Will you two stop it?
Later. That's for dessert.
Just one.
Fine, we'll buy them all.
Mikoy, the food's ready.
I told you not to say that!
Oh, right. You're not Mikoy anymore.
You said it again!
You're Pepito now!
Didn't I tell you not to use Mikoy anymore, Bro?
You said it too!
Hey, enough with the neck slaps!
Come on, let's eat! Let's go!
-Okay, Mom. -Yes, Tess!
-I'll just pay for this. -There!
-Thanks, Bro! -Thank you, thank you po.
This is really good, huh?
-Let's eat! -There we go, come on!
Time to eat!
Mikoy, Chiara, come on!
Sofie!
I told you never to say that!
Come on, Ka Pepe!
Enough with all the head-slapping!
With all the knocking on your heads,
you might all turn into dummies!
That would be great, Mom!
So they won't forget
that they can't call Sis and Bro
by their old names anymore.
It's the secret
of the Pinagpalas.
Oh, come on!
You're the only Pinagpala here, Angelito!
-Tess! -You’re too flirty!
Tess!
-Dekyo! -We have a visitor!
-Who? -Who is it?
-Wow! -Wow!
Mario.
You know, you're really sweet, Dekyo.
A little weird, but sweet.
Thank you, Tess.
Come on, let's eat,
before the flies get to it!
-Mario, they said to eat! -Yes. Let's eat.
Oops, before we eat,
I just want to get everyone's attention.
I just want to say
I'm happy I became part of this family.
That, this is the family I've always dreamed of.
Oh, come on!
Our Rahmboy really is something, huh?
He even has a dramatic speech!
You know,
no crying at the dinner table!
-Come here, baby boy! You need a hug. -Come here!
You need a hug from mommy!
Come on. Join us.
Perfect, the food is ready.
-Hey! That's… The agents! -Hello!
Agent Alex!
‎-Hey! ‎-Hi!
Sorry to interrupt, but
These are your credentials.
Your new identities.
Your identities are different,
but at least you can live normal lives now.
The agency also wants to thank you.
‎-Take that! ‎-Shut it.
Sorry about that.
It's just a reminder that from now on,
we should be called Mr. Pepito and Mrs. Lara
Pinaglaban!
Wow!
Pinaglaban.
That's right. From now on,
the names Mikoy and Chiara are forbidden!
‎Take that too!
-Why? -That's two names!
Enough with the head-slapping.
Come on, let's eat!
-Yes, let's go! -Oh, don't mind us.
We won't stay long,
we just stopped by.
Besides, we're not ready for the beach.
-What? -You're not going to swim?
We're leaving already?
Why?
Can't we go swimming for a little while first?
Oh, no! We can't let this day end
without swimming, okay?
You two are going swimming!
Let's go swimming!
-Let's go! -Wow!
-I thought you weren't ready? -Not ready, huh?
Tess.
Actually, I'm still full!
-We're not hungry! -We'll go swimming first!
That floatie's huge!
All of these are ours now, Tess.
Okay!
-Hey, I'm coming too! -Here.
-Come on, let's eat. -Come on, eat up.
-Agent Alex. -Agent Alex, come here!
Join us, Alex.
Come eat with us!
There's so much food!
Where's my thing, anyone?
You know what would make it even better?
What?
No!
I'm watching a classic Filipino film rerun now…